(Elizabeth:)I'm sorry, I'm rambling.
(Leonard:)-Hi-lo.
SHELDON: Heh, heh.
Hungry? Can I offer you anything?
(Sheldon:)If anyone should offer her anything,
it should be me.
(Sheldon:)Elizabeth, can I get you something?
Perhaps a feminine-hygiene product
or a bowel-regulating yogurt?
(Elizabeth:)Interesting choices.
(Elizabeth:)Based on my current needs,
I guess I'd pick the yogurt.
(Sheldon:)Excellent.
(Sheldon:)If the yogurt works, I bought
some delightful scented candles.
(Leonard:)Look, it's you.
(Elizabeth:)Thank you so much
for opening up your home to me.
(Leonard:)Well, who wants to stay in a hotel?
(Sheldon:)Windows that don't open,
those crazy card-shaped keys.
(Elizabeth:)I'm so glad you understand.
(Sheldon:)No, he doesn't understand.
(Sheldon:)-I understand.
-I understand too.
(Sheldon:)You're just misappropriating
my understanding.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
(Leonard:)I think any university would want you.
Except any university
that already had you...